Contact

ogbekelvin399@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kelvin-ogbeosagie (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Life Coaching

Customer Relationship Management (CRM)

Customer Service

Certifications

Your target audience

Emotional intelligence

Professional postgraduate Diploma in Human Resource Management

Accelerated Jobberman Soft Skill Training

Certified Entrepreneurship Development Professional

Honors-Awards

Best Graduating Student

Kelvin OSAGIE

Founder at PRELA/CEO Authentic Logistics/Content Creator/UI/UX DESIGNER

Benin City, Edo, Nigeria

Summary

Writer, Public Speaker, a graduate of the prestigious University of Benin and a Life coach, above all a lover of God.

He has written two Books, Identify: the cure for poor self esteem and 7 irrefutable How of networking (Currently on Amazon).

He is a Youth/Teen coach on on-time purpose discovery, intentional and Productive living that set them on the path of destiny fulfillment.

He is an advocate of relevant skills for Teen/Youths, students, and young entrepreneurs to be strategically position in the work space.

He is a graduate of the prestigious University of Benin, Benin city, Nigeria with a second class upper degree.

He is passionate about SDG 4, Quality Education for all and has volunteered to see that a reality

He is passionate about volunteering as a means of developing soft and hard skills for personal development and also a means of helping the community and humanity.

He hold Certificate in Human Resource Management(HRM), Health, Safety and Environment(HSE), Project Management(PMP), Digital Marketing and a series of other field

He is the Founder and President of PRELA(Purpose, Relationship and Leadership Academy)

As a relationship coach, he has taught more than 100 students virtually with the likes of Andrew Osas igbineweka, Kenney Erimakonisine, Godwin Uwana, Eragbai Favour and e.t.c, with relevant skills on how Branding and social media can affect their relationships.

He has worked with a number of organizations like Youth Aflame Network International YANI (State Executive Director), Go a Bit Further (Logistics Director), Great Love Foundation, to mention a few

He is passionate about helping the Youth and Teenagers discover purpose on time and not side tracked by wrong relationship.

Experience

The winlos Social Media Manager July 2022 - Present (3 months) Nigeria

Julitech Solutions Internship Trainee June 2022 - Present (4 months) Benin City, Edo, Nigeria

Authentic Logistics Nigeria Managing Director October 2020 - Present (2 years) Benin City, Edo, Nigeria

Self-employed Director June 2019 - Present (3 years 4 months) Benin City, Edo, Nigeria

A coaching programme helping Youth and Teenagers Understand their Purpose

SDG SDG CDS PRESIDENT July 2019 - March 2020 (9 months)

Education

University of Benin

2.1 (Second Class upper) , Plant biology and biotechnology · (2013 - 2017)